<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</title>
    <link>http://oslc.co/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 OSLC; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 09:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://oslc.co/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New and updated tools in Eclipse Lyo: Toolchain Designer &amp; Lyo Store</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20170616-andrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20170616-andrew/</guid>
      <description>In this video, Andrew Berezovskyi, a Lyo project lead will describe the latest support tools that were contributed to Eclipse Lyo, which will further aim the development of OSLC adaptors and toolchains.
  Lyo is an Eclipse project aimed at helping the community adopt OSLC specifications and build OSLC-compliant tools. Learn more about Lyo on https://www.eclipse.org/lyo/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linked Data and OSLC for Tool Interoperability</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20151118-jad-ecs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20151118-jad-ecs/</guid>
      <description>In a lecture given in an OSLC workshop at the Embedded Conference Scandinavia, Jad El-khoury explains the OSLC standard, the underlying linked data technologies that constitute a foundation for the OSLC. After watching the lecture, you will gain a solid understanding of the linked data fundamentals, have a comperehsive overview of various parts of OSLC and be ready to individually work through the workshop material for Eclipse Lyo, an SDK for implementing OSLC-compliant solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get IBM RTC and HP ALM To Blend Together Like Peanut Butter and Jelly</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20151109-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20151109-1/</guid>
      <description>Webinar on integrating HP ALM and IBM RTC, presented by Wesley Coelho, Director of Business Development at Tasktop Technologies, and Lance Knight, Director of Solution Architects at Tasktop.
Watch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tear Down the Walls Between Requirements, Development and Testing</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20151109-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/resources/video-20151109-2/</guid>
      <description>In this webinar, Robert Elves, co-founder of Tasktop Technologies, describes how Business Analysts using Rational Requirements Composer can successfully create and revise Requirements while automatically keeping the Testing team up-to-date on the latest changes through the use of Tasktop Sync.
Watch</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>