<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Group on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</title>
    <link>http://oslc.co/tags/user-group/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Group on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 OSLC; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://oslc.co/tags/user-group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Communications</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/workgroups/communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/workgroups/communications/</guid>
      <description>A working group to discuss, plan, and execute communications about the work of the Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) community. The workgroup aims to build better visibility within the community of the work of the various workgroups; and to raise awareness of the value of the work of the community within the applications and middleware industry and its customers.
 Wiki : Issues: Forum : Workgroup leads :  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra, Extra, Communication User Group is Back</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/news/communication-user-group-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/news/communication-user-group-is-back/</guid>
      <description>The Open Services Communication User Group held its kickoff call on August 13. The team is positioned to highlight integration successes and communicate the benefits of OSLC. As one participant said &amp;ldquo;Think of us as the newspaper for the city.&amp;rdquo; This is a perfect analogy of our intent to be indespensible to the community we serve and relevant to the broader audience. The Communication User Group will aims to deliver value, grows our community and provides the news that you need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>