<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</title>
    <link>http://open-services.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 OSLC; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://open-services.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.4.0 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Short summary Migration to Github is complete; Lyo now supports JSON-LD and Turtle; Lyo Designer generates OpenAPI/Swagger docs and adds modelling support for SHACL shapes. Lyo 2.4 is expected to be the last 2.x release. We also make a switch to a better changelog convention.
✨ Added  JSON-LD support has been added to Lyo Core. Thanks to Ricardo Javier Herrera Ledesma from Koneksys for his effort! Lyo Designer now allows modelling SHACL shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.3.0 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 18:17:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Dear Lyo users,
It is my pleasure to announce on behalf of the project team that Lyo 2.3.0 has been released! 🚀
The release artefacts are available on Maven and the Eclipse plugins are available from Lyo P2 repository.
Notable changes:
 🔥 switch the SDK to use Jena 3.0 🔧 many improvements to Lyo Designer and code generator, including vocabulary modelling view, Turtle support out of the box and switch to user-friendly Bootstrap templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSLC4JS</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/oslc4js/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 15:20:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/oslc4js/</guid>
      <description>OSLC4JS is a set of related open source projects that support the creation and integration of Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC)-based client and server applications that leverage JavaScript and Node.js capabilities. OSLC4JS projects cover the complete end-to-end capabilities required to build, extend, and integrate web apps that exploit OSLC integration capabilities and linked data resources.
Why should I contribute?
Because you’ll see a lot of benefits. Developers will find that it makes it easy to add OSLC capabilities to any Node or Express Web application, including client and server components of that application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.2.0 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 18:17:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to announce today the Lyo 2.2.0 release! The artefacts are available immediately from the Eclipse maven repository, the Lyo Toolchain Designer is available for download from the Lyo P2 update site.
Main features of the 2.2.0 release are:
✨ Lyo Toolchain Designer plugin
The Lyo Toolchain Designer plugin is now officially released as part of the Lyo project. Toolchain Designer allows you to graphically model a complete OSLC toolchain (including interactions between OSLC servers and clients), as well as a single server and/or client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debunking the OSLC Link-Only Myth</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20170715/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 13:24:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20170715/</guid>
      <description>Most large organizations require dozens and sometimes hundreds of specialized software tools to manage the lifecycle of the physical products or software applications they create. It isn&amp;rsquo;t hard to imagine the monumental waste these organizations incur in attempting to manually coordinate the efforts of the teams that use these many disparate tools to create a single product. Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) is an open community for creating specifications for integrating lifecycle activities across tools to address this problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond PLM</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/website-20170825/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 14:54:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/website-20170825/</guid>
      <description>A blog, by Oleg Shilovitsky, for the community of people looking for information about Engineering and Manufacturing Software. This has much information relevant for the OSLC community.
Visit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Groups</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-groups/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the Conversation</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-join/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evangelise</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-evangelise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-evangelise/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specifications</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-specifications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add to this Site</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-content/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing OSLC Applications</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/developing-oslc-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/developing-oslc-applications/</guid>
      <description>Get started with developing OSLC applications “OSL-whaaaat now?”
Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) is a community that writes specifications to integrate software. Learn more at Why develop OSLC applications and at our main site.
For a high-level overview of how to add OSLC support to software, we recommend our video &amp;ldquo;Getting started on implementing OSLC&amp;ldquo;:
  The description on YouTube includes a table of contents and links to references.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-share/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-share/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/contribute/ct-development/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New and updated tools in Eclipse Lyo: Toolchain Designer &amp; Lyo Store</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20170616-andrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20170616-andrew/</guid>
      <description>In this video, Andrew Berezovskyi, a Lyo project lead will describe the latest support tools that were contributed to Eclipse Lyo, which will further aim the development of OSLC adaptors and toolchains.
  Lyo is an Eclipse project aimed at helping the community adopt OSLC specifications and build OSLC-compliant tools. Learn more about Lyo on https://www.eclipse.org/lyo/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.1.2 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 23:21:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.1.2/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse Lyo 2.1.2 has been released today! This was the first release carried out by Jad El-khoury, Jim Amsden, and yours truly. We went through a release review process even though it is not strictly needed for the service releases just in order to get acquainted with the process.
This release has mainly addressed issues in the client (28 issues) and core (9 issues). I would like to thank all contributors who submitted the patches!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ALM-PLM Interoperability Survey</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/alm-plm-interoperability-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/alm-plm-interoperability-survey/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in ALM-PLM Interoperability, please participate in this survey - ALM / PLM Interoperability and OSLC questionnaire, https://vpe-umfrage.mv.uni-kl.de/index.php/748615/lang-en .
The ProSTEP iViP Association and the Institute for Virtual Product development would like to invite you to participate in this questionnaire. Please take about 10 minutes of your time to complete the questionnaire.
The results will help to initiate the ALM-PLM Interoperability Workflow Forum from the ProSTEP iViP Association.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OLSC Survey Provides Insights into Needs for Software Integration Standards</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-survey-provides-insights-software-integration-standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-survey-provides-insights-software-integration-standards/</guid>
      <description>The Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) steering committee is gathering feedback from the community to help shape the future vision and mission for OSLC. As part of that effort a survey of the community members was conducted and it highlights some interesting results about the needs of this group. You can find the full results of the survey at https://www.surveymonkey.com/results/SM-2XVJT6CR/.
OSLC is an open community that builds standards to solve a vexing problem: How to integrate the specialized software used by different types of software and systems development practitioners so teams and their tools can work together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSLC3 Update: What is it, how is it different, and why is it important?</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oslc3-update-what-how-why-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oslc3-update-what-how-why-important/</guid>
      <description>Open Services for Life-cycle Collaboration or OSLC defines a set of standard capabilities enabling loosely coupled, open and scalable point-to-point integration between heterogeneous software development tools. OSLC allows users to work seamlessly across their preferred tools and does not require complex interchange of data between tools that may result in information redundancy and maintenance issues.
The OASIS OSLC Core 3.0 Specifications represent the continued evolution of OSLC through collaborating organizations to provide the standards, APIs and tools that support integrated product, system and application lifecycle management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linked Data and OSLC for Tool Interoperability</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151118-jad-ecs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151118-jad-ecs/</guid>
      <description>In a lecture given in an OSLC workshop at the Embedded Conference Scandinavia, Jad El-khoury explains the OSLC standard, the underlying linked data technologies that constitute a foundation for the OSLC. After watching the lecture, you will gain a solid understanding of the linked data fundamentals, have a comperehsive overview of various parts of OSLC and be ready to individually work through the workshop material for Eclipse Lyo, an SDK for implementing OSLC-compliant solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROSTEP OpenPDM OSLC Adapter Product Overview</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171117/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171117/</guid>
      <description>The PROSTEP OpenPDM OSLC Adapter makes your PLM system(s) available to the OSLC world. It offers OSLC standard services, especially for those PLM systems which don’t offer native ones. The adapter is an add-on for the OpenPDM integration framework which provides connectors to a wide range of systems. The OpenPDM OSLC services can be integrated in any OSLC consuming applications. The gap between ALM and PLM can be closed.
This presentation provides details on the OpenPDM OSLC Adapter including overview, reference project and technical information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROSTEP AG Announces OpenPDM OSLC Adapter</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/prostep-ag-announces-openpdm-oslc-adapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/prostep-ag-announces-openpdm-oslc-adapter/</guid>
      <description>PROSTEP would like to announce to the OSLC community, that there is an OpenPDM OSLC Adapter which enables PLM systems to connect to the OSLC world. It offers OSLC standard services, especially for those PLM systems which don’t offer native ones. The adapter is an add-on for the OpenPDM integration framework which provides connectors to a wide range of systems, e.g.:
Ansys EKM Aras Innovator Autodesk Vault Dassault SmarTeam Dassault ENOVIA V6 Dassault ENOVIA VPM V4 MSC SimManager Oracle Agile ePLM PTC Windchill SAP PLM Siemens Teamcenter Engineering Siemens Teamcenter Enterprise Siemens Teamcenter UA The OpenPDM OSLC services can be integrated in any OSLC consuming applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Technical Committee</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/workgroups/core-tc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/workgroups/core-tc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domains Technical Committee</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/workgroups/domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/workgroups/domains/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get IBM RTC and HP ALM To Blend Together Like Peanut Butter and Jelly</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-1/</guid>
      <description>Webinar on integrating HP ALM and IBM RTC, presented by Wesley Coelho, Director of Business Development at Tasktop Technologies, and Lance Knight, Director of Solution Architects at Tasktop.
Watch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steering Committee</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/workgroups/steering-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/workgroups/steering-committee/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasktop: Helping a Center of Excellence live up to its name</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171109/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171109/</guid>
      <description>Tasktop Sync Case Study on enabling the customer to increase both velocity AND quality.
View</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Integration requires a combination of linking and syncing</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20151109/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20151109/</guid>
      <description>In this article, Tasktop explores the strengths of Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) and some of the areas of improvement. The conclusion is that flexibility and value are what drive integration decisions.
Read</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tear Down the Walls Between Requirements, Development and Testing</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-2/</guid>
      <description>In this webinar, Robert Elves, co-founder of Tasktop Technologies, describes how Business Analysts using Rational Requirements Composer can successfully create and revise Requirements while automatically keeping the Testing team up-to-date on the latest changes through the use of Tasktop Sync.
Watch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn more about Tasktop Sync 4.3 (July 2015)</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/learn-more-about-tasktop-sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/learn-more-about-tasktop-sync/</guid>
      <description>Tasktop, the leader in Software Lifecycle Integration (SLI) and creator of the Eclipse Mylyn open source tool, today announced the latest versions of its Tasktop Sync and Tasktop Data products, which add strategic new tools to its integration network and provide a vastly superior user experience.
Tasktop products enable enterprises to achieve major gains by connecting everyone in the software lifecycle to create one efficient development and delivery team. With Tasktop solutions, everyone can use their various tools of choice and still collaborate in real time as if they were all working on a single platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New OASIS OSLC Steering Committee Announced</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/new-oasis-oslc-steering-committee-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/new-oasis-oslc-steering-committee-announced/</guid>
      <description>The September 2015 elections for the OASIS OSLC Steering Committee have concluded &amp;ndash; congratulations to the new and re-elected members!
Also noteworthy is that as of this election, the number of Steering Committee members increased from 7 to 9. The expanded breadth and experience that is represented in the new Steering Committee will further enhance its ability to guide and serve the OSLC Member Section and community. A warm welcome to the OSLC Steering Committee for September 2015-2016:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra, Extra, Communication User Group is Back</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/communication-user-group-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/communication-user-group-is-back/</guid>
      <description>The Open Services Communication User Group held its kickoff call on August 13. The team is positioned to highlight integration successes and communicate the benefits of OSLC. As one participant said &amp;ldquo;Think of us as the newspaper for the city.&amp;rdquo; This is a perfect analogy of our intent to be indespensible to the community we serve and relevant to the broader audience. The Communication User Group will aims to deliver value, grows our community and provides the news that you need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OASIS OSLC Steering Committee Elections Coming Soon</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oasis-oslc-steering-committee-elections-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oasis-oslc-steering-committee-elections-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Whether you live in the I/T or Systems world, software integration in heterogeneous environments can represent both a challenge (where do I even start?) and opportunity (how can I advance my environment to provide more value, deliver faster and with reduced risk?).
Communities like openservices and OASIS OSLC collaboratively discuss lifecycle integration challenges and solutions that leverage open standards. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re here to contribute your knowledge and experience or to learn from others, we&amp;rsquo;re all in it together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pardon our dust: updated design rolling out gradually</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/updated-design-rolling-out-gradually/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/updated-design-rolling-out-gradually/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned almost a year ago, I’ve been plugging away at a new look and feel for this site. I have a project on GitHub; you can open issues or discuss the direction in general; you can look at proposed sample pages.
And as of today, you’ll be able to see how it looks live. I’ll be rolling out elements of it gradually. There are a number of moving parts and I want to test thoroughly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSLC at IBM InterConnect 2015</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-ibm-interconnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-ibm-interconnect/</guid>
      <description>Coming in a couple weeks is IBM&amp;rsquo;s new InterConnect conference which brings together past IBM events (Innovate, Pulse, Impact) into one. These conferences often contain a number of sessions and events with OSLC connect. As you are building your agenda for the conference, I wanted to highlight my sample agenda which has some key sessions that either talking directly about OSLC activities or other topics that are key to OSLC activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSLC4Net</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20130121/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20130121/</guid>
      <description>A toolkit for developing OSLC consumers and providers for .NET environments that contains the following tools:
 OSLC4NET SDK, which is very similar to the OSLC4J component of Eclipse Lyo: you can model OSLC resources as .NET objects, annotate them with OSLC attributes, and use the REST services provided by ASP.NET MVC 4 for HTTP requests and request handling. OSLC Change Management consumer implementation in the form of a test suite  Go</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20111111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20111111/</guid>
      <description>The Eclipse Lyo project focuses on providing an SDK to help the Eclipse community to adopt OSLC specifications and build OSLC-compliant tools. The source code is available in a Git repository.
 OSLC4J: A Java toolkit to help you build OSLC-ready Java applications Test suites: Verify that your OSLC implementations are compliant with the specifications Reference Implementations: See how OSLC functions with working samples  Go</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/ns/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/ns/readme/</guid>
      <description> Converting RDF files Use Jena command line tools to produce the files in other formats:
riot --output turtle core.rdf &amp;gt; core.ttl  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/specifications/archive/core-2.0/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/specifications/archive/core-2.0/readme/</guid>
      <description>The conversion is done via:
pandoc --from twiki --to markdown_mmd -o _index.md source.twiki  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>