<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working Group on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</title>
    <link>http://oslc.co/tags/working-group/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working Group on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 OSLC; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://oslc.co/tags/working-group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ALM-PLM Interoperability</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/workgroups/alm-plm-interoperability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/workgroups/alm-plm-interoperability/</guid>
      <description>The working group ALM-PLM Interoperability (2nd edition) aims to define industrial relevant scenarios for interoperability of ALM and PLM engineering environment to indicate gaps and potential extensions to the relevant OASIS OSLC technical committees. It builds on the work of the previous Working Group “ALM-PLM Interoperability (1st edition)”
 Wiki : Issues: Forum : Workgroup leads :  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human factors</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/workgroups/human-factors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/workgroups/human-factors/</guid>
      <description>The Human factors (HF) working group resources will define a set of use cases and scenarios that will feed the concepts necessary for exchange in order facilitate the use of human factors in systems engineering. The term &amp;lsquo;systems engineering&amp;rsquo; is used to describe the interdisciplinary field of engineering that focuses on the design and management of a system over the whole lifecycle.
HF is the application of human factors methods to develop systems with an effective, comfortable and user friendly design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifecycle Integration Patterns</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/workgroups/lifecycle-integration-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/workgroups/lifecycle-integration-patterns/</guid>
      <description>This working group will define a framework to support the creation and consumption of lifecycle patterns that will enable practitioners to apply OSLC specifications and concept and quickly locate solutions to common lifecycle integration challenges. Experienced users who have successfully appied OSLC in their environments are invited to share parts of their solution as additional patterns.
 Wiki : https://github.com/OSLC/lifecycle-integration-patterns/wiki Issues: https://github.com/OSLC/lifecycle-integration-patterns/issues Forum : http://discourse.oslc.co/c/working-groups/lifecycle-integration-patterns Workgroup leads : Rainer Ersch, Wesley Coelho  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steering Committee</title>
      <link>http://oslc.co/workgroups/steering-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oslc.co/workgroups/steering-committee/</guid>
      <description>The Steering Committee, now operating at OASIS, is the governing body of the OSLC community that approves new workgroups, approves specifications, de-commissions workgroups, and manages other changes in governance or participation across the community.
At oasis-open.org
 Wiki : Issues: Forum : Workgroup leads :  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>