<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</title>
    <link>http://open-services.net/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 OSLC; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://open-services.net/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OSLC4JS</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/oslc4js/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 15:20:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/oslc4js/</guid>
      <description>OSLC4JS is a set of related open source projects that support the creation and integration of Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC)-based client and server applications that leverage JavaScript and Node.js capabilities. OSLC4JS projects cover the complete end-to-end capabilities required to build, extend, and integrate web apps that exploit OSLC integration capabilities and linked data resources.
Why should I contribute?
Because you’ll see a lot of benefits. Developers will find that it makes it easy to add OSLC capabilities to any Node or Express Web application, including client and server components of that application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debunking the OSLC Link-Only Myth</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20170715/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 13:24:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20170715/</guid>
      <description>Most large organizations require dozens and sometimes hundreds of specialized software tools to manage the lifecycle of the physical products or software applications they create. It isn&amp;rsquo;t hard to imagine the monumental waste these organizations incur in attempting to manually coordinate the efforts of the teams that use these many disparate tools to create a single product. Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) is an open community for creating specifications for integrating lifecycle activities across tools to address this problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond PLM</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/website-20170825/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 14:54:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/website-20170825/</guid>
      <description>A blog, by Oleg Shilovitsky, for the community of people looking for information about Engineering and Manufacturing Software. This has much information relevant for the OSLC community.
Visit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing OSLC Applications</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/developing-oslc-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/developing-oslc-applications/</guid>
      <description>Get started with developing OSLC applications “OSL-whaaaat now?”
Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) is a community that writes specifications to integrate software. Learn more at Why develop OSLC applications and at our main site.
For a high-level overview of how to add OSLC support to software, we recommend our video &amp;ldquo;Getting started on implementing OSLC&amp;ldquo;:
  The description on YouTube includes a table of contents and links to references.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New and updated tools in Eclipse Lyo: Toolchain Designer &amp; Lyo Store</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20170616-andrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20170616-andrew/</guid>
      <description>In this video, Andrew Berezovskyi, a Lyo project lead will describe the latest support tools that were contributed to Eclipse Lyo, which will further aim the development of OSLC adaptors and toolchains.
  Lyo is an Eclipse project aimed at helping the community adopt OSLC specifications and build OSLC-compliant tools. Learn more about Lyo on https://www.eclipse.org/lyo/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linked Data and OSLC for Tool Interoperability</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151118-jad-ecs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151118-jad-ecs/</guid>
      <description>In a lecture given in an OSLC workshop at the Embedded Conference Scandinavia, Jad El-khoury explains the OSLC standard, the underlying linked data technologies that constitute a foundation for the OSLC. After watching the lecture, you will gain a solid understanding of the linked data fundamentals, have a comperehsive overview of various parts of OSLC and be ready to individually work through the workshop material for Eclipse Lyo, an SDK for implementing OSLC-compliant solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROSTEP OpenPDM OSLC Adapter Product Overview</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171117/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171117/</guid>
      <description>The PROSTEP OpenPDM OSLC Adapter makes your PLM system(s) available to the OSLC world. It offers OSLC standard services, especially for those PLM systems which don’t offer native ones. The adapter is an add-on for the OpenPDM integration framework which provides connectors to a wide range of systems. The OpenPDM OSLC services can be integrated in any OSLC consuming applications. The gap between ALM and PLM can be closed.
This presentation provides details on the OpenPDM OSLC Adapter including overview, reference project and technical information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get IBM RTC and HP ALM To Blend Together Like Peanut Butter and Jelly</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-1/</guid>
      <description>Webinar on integrating HP ALM and IBM RTC, presented by Wesley Coelho, Director of Business Development at Tasktop Technologies, and Lance Knight, Director of Solution Architects at Tasktop.
Watch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasktop: Helping a Center of Excellence live up to its name</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171109/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/presentation-20171109/</guid>
      <description>Tasktop Sync Case Study on enabling the customer to increase both velocity AND quality.
View</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Integration requires a combination of linking and syncing</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20151109/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/article-20151109/</guid>
      <description>In this article, Tasktop explores the strengths of Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration (OSLC) and some of the areas of improvement. The conclusion is that flexibility and value are what drive integration decisions.
Read</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tear Down the Walls Between Requirements, Development and Testing</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/video-20151109-2/</guid>
      <description>In this webinar, Robert Elves, co-founder of Tasktop Technologies, describes how Business Analysts using Rational Requirements Composer can successfully create and revise Requirements while automatically keeping the Testing team up-to-date on the latest changes through the use of Tasktop Sync.
Watch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSLC4Net</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20130121/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20130121/</guid>
      <description>A toolkit for developing OSLC consumers and providers for .NET environments that contains the following tools:
 OSLC4NET SDK, which is very similar to the OSLC4J component of Eclipse Lyo: you can model OSLC resources as .NET objects, annotate them with OSLC attributes, and use the REST services provided by ASP.NET MVC 4 for HTTP requests and request handling. OSLC Change Management consumer implementation in the form of a test suite  Go</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20111111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 20:57:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-services.net/resources/tool-20111111/</guid>
      <description>The Eclipse Lyo project focuses on providing an SDK to help the Eclipse community to adopt OSLC specifications and build OSLC-compliant tools. The source code is available in a Git repository.
 OSLC4J: A Java toolkit to help you build OSLC-ready Java applications Test suites: Verify that your OSLC implementations are compliant with the specifications Reference Implementations: See how OSLC functions with working samples  Go</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>