<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</title>
    <link>http://open-services.net/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on OSLC - Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 18:25:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://open-services.net/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Change Management v3.0 approved as the first OASIS Standard from an Open Project</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/chg-mgmt-oasis-stnd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 18:25:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/chg-mgmt-oasis-stnd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OASIS is pleased to announce that the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oasis-open.org/committees/ballot.php?id=3619&#34;&gt;Call for Consent&lt;/a&gt; has closed and, effective 26 May 2021, &lt;strong&gt;OSLC Change Management Version 3.0&lt;/strong&gt; is an OASIS Standard according to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oasis-open.org/policies-guidelines/tc-process-2017-05-26#OScallForConsent&#34;&gt;Call for Consent procedure&lt;/a&gt;. Project Administration will now undertake the final tasks of preparing and loading the standard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Change Management Version 3.0 was one of the first approved Project Specifications to come out of the new OASIS Open Project Program and its first OASIS Standard. The Project Governing Board will be acting on additional deliverables over the next few months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSLC OP publishes four new Project Specifications</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/newprjspecs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/newprjspecs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OASIS is pleased to announce that OSLC Core v3.0, OSLC Query v3.0, OSLC Requirements Management v2.1, and OSLC Change Management v3.0 are now approved \OASIS Project Specifications. These join the previously announced OSLC Quality Management v2.1 as the first approved Project Specifications from the Open Projects program.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;OSLC Core&lt;/em&gt; defines the overall approach to Open Services for Lifecycle Collaboration that extend and complement the W3C Linked Data Platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;OSLC Query&lt;/em&gt; provides a mechanism for a client to search for RDF resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSLCFest 2020</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oslcfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oslcfest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The OSLCFest took place on May 18-20, 2020. There were a total of 20 presentations on OSLC, including 8 presentations by tool vendors. The recording of the talks of the OSLCFest 2020 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.oslcfest.org/&#34;&gt;http://www.oslcfest.org/&lt;/a&gt;) can be found on YouTube:&#xA;Day1: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FxMAyHqEay8&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FxMAyHqEay8&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;Day2: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tz35ecvqLlQ&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tz35ecvqLlQ&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;Day3: &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/t1AJg8HAEn4&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/t1AJg8HAEn4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSLC Open Project first spec draft publication</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/0912-cm-psd03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 18:05:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/0912-cm-psd03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We finally have some great news to share! After starting the OSLC Open Project in May 2019 and having&#xA;a long summer with various people being off for vacations, we have prepared the first&#xA;specification for publication, updated the templates and fixed major outstanding issues. The OSLC&#xA;OP Project Governing Board &lt;a href=&#34;https://lists.oasis-open-projects.org/g/oslc-op-pgb/message/27&#34;&gt;has approved&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;the publication of the Change Management 2.1 PSD (Project Specification Draft) 03.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This specification defines the OSLC Change Management domain, a RESTful web services interface for&#xA;the management of product change requests, activities, tasks and relationships between those and&#xA;related resources such as requirements, test cases, or architectural resources. To support these&#xA;scenarios, this specification defines a set of HTTP-based RESTful interfaces in terms of HTTP&#xA;methods: GET, POST, PUT and DELETE, HTTP response codes, content type handling and resource formats.&#xA;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://open-services.net/specifications/&#34;&gt;table of all specs&lt;/a&gt; has been updated to point to the&#xA;newly published draft, which is available in the OASIS repository for OSLC specs: &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.oasis-open-projects.org/oslc-op/cm/v3.0/psd03/change-mgt-spec.html&#34;&gt;OSLC CM 2.1&#xA;PSD 03&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSLC Open Project announcement</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/0903-open-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 11:05:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/0903-open-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce a big step forward for OSLC!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most exciting thing that we heard throughout the OSLCfest 2018 conference was that people were&#xA;eager to contribute and were asking for a simpler, more streamlined way to provide contributions and&#xA;make their voices heard. After exploring several alternatives, the OSLC Steering Committee decided&#xA;to shift ongoing work from the OASIS Technical Committees to a new OSLC Open Project under the&#xA;recently-announced &lt;a href=&#34;https://oasis-open-projects.org/&#34;&gt;OASIS Open Project program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.4.0 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;short-summary&#34;&gt;Short summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Migration to Github is complete; Lyo now supports JSON-LD and Turtle; Lyo Designer generates OpenAPI/Swagger docs and adds modelling support for SHACL shapes. Lyo 2.4 is expected to be the last 2.x release. We also make a switch to a &lt;a href=&#34;https://keepachangelog.com/en/1.0.0/&#34;&gt;better changelog convention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-added&#34;&gt;✨ Added&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;JSON-LD support has been added to Lyo Core. Thanks to Ricardo Javier Herrera Ledesma from Koneksys for his effort!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lyo Designer now allows modelling SHACL shapes. Code generation of SHACL shapes has not been implemented yet. If this is something you need, get in touch! Thanks to Yash Khatri from SCANIA for this contribution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lyo Designer now allows to generate OpenAPI/Swagger documentation for your OSLC Server; see the details below. Thanks to Jad El-khoury and SCANIA for this contribution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Turtle support is now turned on by default in Lyo Designer for the generated code.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/eclipse/lyo.store/issues/28&#34;&gt;Support for OSLC Query&lt;/a&gt; has been added to Lyo Store. Thanks to Jad El-khoury and SCANIA for this contribution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;OpenJDK 11 has been added to the test matrix for most repos. JDK 11 is not yet supported officially, however.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/eclipse/lyo&#34;&gt;lyo&lt;/a&gt; repository has been added to manage all cross-cutting issues that span multiple repos.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kotlinlang.org&#34;&gt;Kotlin&lt;/a&gt; is now used for unit tests in Lyo Core.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swagger Docs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.3.0 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 18:17:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2018-eclipse-lyo-2.3.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Lyo users,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is my pleasure to announce on behalf of the project team that Lyo 2.3.0 has been released! 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The release artefacts are available on Maven and the Eclipse plugins are available from &lt;a href=&#34;http://download.eclipse.org/lyo/p2/stable/&#34;&gt;Lyo P2 repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notable changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🔥 switch the SDK to use Jena 3.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🔧 many improvements to Lyo Designer and code generator, including vocabulary modelling view, Turtle support out of the box and switch to user-friendly Bootstrap templates.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✨ new library for validation against constraints defined either as SHACL or OSLC Resource Shapes &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/eclipse/lyo-validation&#34;&gt;https://github.com/eclipse/lyo-validation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://projects.eclipse.org/projects/technology.lyo/releases/2.3.0&#34;&gt;2.3.0 release page&lt;/a&gt; on Eclipse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.2.0 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 18:17:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to announce today the Lyo 2.2.0 release! The artefacts are available immediately from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://repo.eclipse.org/content/repositories/lyo-releases/org/eclipse/lyo/&#34;&gt;Eclipse maven repository&lt;/a&gt;, the Lyo Toolchain Designer is available for download from the &lt;a href=&#34;http://download.eclipse.org/lyo/p2/releases/2.2.0&#34;&gt;Lyo P2 update site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Main features of the 2.2.0 release are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;✨ &lt;strong&gt;Lyo Toolchain Designer plugin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Lyo Toolchain Designer plugin is now officially released as part of the Lyo project. Toolchain Designer allows you to graphically model a complete OSLC toolchain (including interactions between OSLC servers and clients), as well as a single server and/or client. From such models, the Lyo Code Generator can then automatically generate an almost complete OSLC4J-compliant Java web project. To model and generate your first toolchain, follow the &lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.eclipse.org/Lyo/ToolchainModellingAndCodeGenerationWorkshop&#34;&gt;Lyo Designer tutorial&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Lyo 2.1.2 release</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 23:21:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/2017-eclipse-lyo-2.1.2/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse Lyo 2.1.2 is the first release since 2013 done by the new release team and fixes many issues in Lyo Core &amp;amp; Lyo Client.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALM-PLM Interoperability Survey</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/alm-plm-interoperability-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/alm-plm-interoperability-survey/</guid>
      <description>Please participate in this survey, the results will help to initiate the ALM-PLM Interoperability Workflow Forum from the ProSTEP iViP Association</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLSC Survey Provides Insights into Needs for Software Integration Standards</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-survey-provides-insights-software-integration-standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-survey-provides-insights-software-integration-standards/</guid>
      <description>The OSLC steering committee is gathering feedback from the community to help shape the future vision and mission for OSLC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSLC3 Update: What is it, how is it different, and why is it important?</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oslc3-update-what-how-why-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oslc3-update-what-how-why-important/</guid>
      <description>The OASIS OSLC Core 3.0 Specifications represent the continued evolution of OSLC through collaborating organizations to provide the standards, APIs and tools that support integrated product, system and application lifecycle management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROSTEP AG Announces OpenPDM OSLC Adapter</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/prostep-ag-announces-openpdm-oslc-adapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/prostep-ag-announces-openpdm-oslc-adapter/</guid>
      <description>OpenPDM OSLC Adapter enables PLM systems to connect to the OSLC world. It offers OSLC standard services, especially for those PLM systems which don’t offer native ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn more about Tasktop Sync 4.3 (July 2015)</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/learn-more-about-tasktop-sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/learn-more-about-tasktop-sync/</guid>
      <description>Tasktop announced the latest versions of its Tasktop Sync and Tasktop Data products, which add strategic new tools to its integration network and provide a vastly superior user experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New OASIS OSLC Steering Committee Announced</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/new-oasis-oslc-steering-committee-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/new-oasis-oslc-steering-committee-announced/</guid>
      <description>The September 2015 elections for the OASIS OSLC Steering Committee have concluded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra, Extra, Communication User Group is Back</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/communication-user-group-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/communication-user-group-is-back/</guid>
      <description>The Open Services Communication User Group held its kickoff call on August 13. The team is positioned to highlight integration successes and communicate the benefits of OSLC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OASIS OSLC Steering Committee Elections Coming Soon</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oasis-oslc-steering-committee-elections-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oasis-oslc-steering-committee-elections-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in working with other leaders in this space and helping influence the direction and expansion of OSLC, consider becoming a member of OASIS OSLC Steering Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pardon our dust: updated design rolling out gradually</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/updated-design-rolling-out-gradually/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/updated-design-rolling-out-gradually/</guid>
      <description>The updated site is live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSLC at IBM InterConnect 2015</title>
      <link>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-ibm-interconnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://open-services.net/news/oslc-ibm-interconnect/</guid>
      <description>Coming in a couple weeks is IBM&amp;rsquo;s new InterConnect conference which brings together past IBM events (Innovate, Pulse, Impact) into one.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
